a short video about STS or quick single
有关STS的简短视频或快速单曲
navigation feature we're going to show
我们将要展示的导航功能
this fisherperson envious code and then
这个渔夫羡慕的代码，然后
switch to eclipse
切换到日食
so suppose a grace code would like to
所以假设宽限码想
look for owners requests nothing
寻找主人什么都没要求
definition so we have to activate our
定义，所以我们必须激活我们的
cook similar relation feature and we
烹饪类似的关系特征，我们
have to go to this go menu and click on
必须转到此转到菜单，然后单击
go to simple works because it's also a
去简单的作品，因为它也是一个
shortcut first it shows us the list of
快捷方式首先它向我们显示了
all symbols of work basically like Pat
所有工作符号基本上都像Pat
it has to be on need spring symbols so
它必须需要Spring 符号，所以
this list is full of various spring
这个清单充满了各种春天
symbols such as spinning annotations and
符号，例如旋转注释和
request mappings beans so if we type at
请求映射bean，所以如果我们键入
plus they're gonna see only beans we
而且他们只会看到我们的beans
type at slash we can I see all the
输入斜线，我们可以看到所有
request mappings and if we start typing
请求映射，如果我们开始输入
further we can narrow down this list to
进一步，我们可以缩小列表的范围
something more meaningful so this is the
更有意义的事情，这是
oldest request back and so as you can
最早的请求回来，所以你可以
see each entry in the list is a cross
看到列表中的每个条目都是一个十字
mapping path that our customer ping type
客户ping类型的映射路径
and the researcher is defined so if you
和研究人员的定义，所以如果你
click on it it takes us right to the
点击它，便带我们前往
definition of this request mapping in
该请求映射的定义
the code there are also other things
代码中还有其他东西
here and thus list right such as beans
在这里，因此列出权利，例如beans
so we can also look for any beans and if
所以我们也可以寻找任何 Bean type ，如果
we click on Rapids it has to take us the
我们单击急流，必须带我们
place in the color it has been is
颜色一直是
defined so for example all those
定义，例如所有这些
properties is components and it takes us
属性是组成部分，这需要我们
right to its definition so let's examine
它定义的权利，所以让我们研究一下
the same feature in Eclipse so this is
Eclipse中的相​​同功能，所以这是
the SDS for Eclipse version so the same
SDS for Eclipse版本也是如此
feature can be activated by pressing
可以通过按激活功能
come on six
来吧六
but it starts with symbols in in
但它以in中的符号开头
currently opens file if you type come on
当前打开文件，如果您键入加油
six again as it states down below it's
再次向下六次
gonna show you all the all the workspace
会告诉你所有的工作空间
symbols ok so let's try and look for
好的符号，让我们尝试寻找
some beans for example I what I find
例如一些 bean 我找到了
older search service
较旧的搜索服务
so it's like at the plus to look at the
所以就像看加号一样
beans and then older search service so
bean ，然后是较旧的搜索服务，因此
this is it
就是这个
right so the click on earth is gonna
对，所以点击地球会
take us right to its definition right
带我们去定义它的权利
and the definition is here right it's
定义就在这里
under this and being annotation we can
在此之下，并成为注释，我们可以
also look her for other things like
也找她找其他东西
spring annotations for example you can
春季注释，例如，您可以
say add components and look for all
说添加组件并查找所有
components in our code sorry we have to
我们代码中的组件很抱歉，我们必须
press command 6 again to look at the
再次按命令6查看
workspace symbols alright so as you
工作区符号就可以了
scroll down through the list you could
向下滚动列表，您可以
see that for example odors controller is
看到例如气味控制器
under F component right if we click on
在F组件下，如果单击
it there is no F component annotation
它没有F组件注释
anywhere near it
靠近它的任何地方
but controller and a patient is met
但是遇见管制员和病人
annotated with the component annotation
带有组件注释的注释
so every controller is a component right
所以每个控制器都是正确的组件
so as you can see this is this
就像你看到的那样
inheritance meta inheritance is
继承元继承是
accounted for in this search as you look
在您的搜索中占比
at at the entry it shows in the summary
在摘要中显示的条目中
of the little in the inheritance
遗产中的一点
relationship between annotations that
注释之间的关系
you see here we can also search for
您在这里看到我们也可以搜索
example for something that doesn't even
甚至没有的例子
have annotations for example being
有例如注释
patrick was a 3/8 so if we open it up
帕特里克（Patrick）是3/8，所以如果我们打开它
there are no limitations but as yes or
没有限制，但是是或
to limit recognizes this classes as a
限制将此类视为
mean that's contributed by spring dog
意思是春狗贡献的
there is also a little extra to similar
还有一些额外的类似
negation you can also look at life
否定也可以看生活
request mappings if you type slash slash
如果输入斜线，则请求映射
so but that does only active if your
因此，只有在您的
application is running and there is a
应用程序正在运行，并且有一个
and actuator start there alone it's
和执行器就从那里开始
right so if you click on it's kind of
对，所以如果您单击它
take you to the URL on the browser so
带您到浏览器上的URL，以便
this is it this is a quick or over the
这是它是快速还是结束
overview of
大致的了解
quick similar aviation fishin STS for
快速类似的航空钓鱼STS
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
you
您